{"qid": "easy-hupd-0001", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0002", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2011 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "Organic-Inorganic Hybrid Multilayer Gate Dielectrics for Thin-Film Transistors"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0003", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0004", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number.", "answer": 10.981981981981981}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0005", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0006", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 562.1001681479702}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0007", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2018? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28", "F42"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0008", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0009", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Matthew Marquez"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0010", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 322.1840837119648}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0011", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2010? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A42", "A43", "A44", "A62"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0012", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2011? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B06", "B07", "B61"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0013", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number.", "answer": 2.1531531531531534}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0014", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 2.0908094281015894}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0015", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0016", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2015 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 609.4677191993234}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0017", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 4 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2005? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A46", "B30", "B44"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0018", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0019", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number.", "answer": 0.08899524524524524}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0020", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2012 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0021", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0022", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0023", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0024", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2014? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B03", "B07", "B27"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0025", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2004? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A42", "B04", "B07", "B31"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0026", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2013 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0027", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 2.289958158995816}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0028", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2009? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A41", "A44", "B02"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0029", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0030", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0031", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have more than 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.20725244072524407}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0032", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2016 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 538.8956416464891}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0033", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2007? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A46", "B04"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0034", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 575.5098376783079}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0035", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2012 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0036", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have exactly 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.026499302649930265}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0037", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2014? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B03", "B07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0038", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number.", "answer": 0.448974569319114}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0039", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0040", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0041", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2011 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 88.16663164530364}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0042", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 6 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0043", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2011 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 160.51191823575815}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0044", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2014 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0045", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9656903765690377}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0046", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have greater than or equal to 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.702928870292887}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0047", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2013 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0048", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0049", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0050", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have more than 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07670850767085077}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0051", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have exactly 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.18828451882845187}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0052", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0053", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Matthew Marquez"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0054", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.18828451882845187}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0055", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2010 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Telenostics point of performance pre-operations condition capture system"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0056", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 4.625941422594142}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0057", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2017 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0058", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2010? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A42", "A43"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0059", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0060", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have greater than or equal to 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.20725244072524407}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0061", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number.", "answer": 5.1475483580746735}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0062", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR PRODUCING TLR5 AGONIST PROTEIN"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0063", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 120.16295320465089}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0064", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2017? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17", "G11"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0065", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number.", "answer": 4.353571428571429}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0066", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 4 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2014? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B03", "B07", "B27"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0067", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0068", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 9.114870881567231}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0069", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.7927475592747559}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0070", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 8 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0071", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2010 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "DYNAMIC TISSUE HOLDING DEVICE WITH LOW PROFILE SPRING"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0072", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number.", "answer": 2.3697553743513713}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0073", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0074", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 205.07628938258622}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0075", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2013 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0076", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0077", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2014 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0078", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0079", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2014 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 224.18518914297928}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0080", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 13.375732217573221}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0081", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2016 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0082", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2016 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0083", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 2 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0084", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2011 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "Organic-Inorganic Hybrid Multilayer Gate Dielectrics for Thin-Film Transistors"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0085", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 0.2779406017975772}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0086", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0087", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0088", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 0.1534845132743363}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0089", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number.", "answer": 7.532104969290899}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0090", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number.", "answer": 1.6135135135135135}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0091", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0092", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 317.93790760869564}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0093", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2011 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0094", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0095", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2015? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B06", "B28"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0096", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2016? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0097", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0098", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0099", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0100", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0101", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0102", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0103", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have greater than or equal to 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.20725244072524407}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0104", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2017 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0105", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2016? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0106", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2010 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0107", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0108", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2012? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A23", "A41"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0109", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Matthew Marquez"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0110", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number.", "answer": 0.4057079318013343}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0111", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2017 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 343.4315992292871}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0112", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0113", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2017 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 289.35227272727275}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0114", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 2.533392698130009}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0115", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2007? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A46", "B04"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0116", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 1.5287610619469028}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0117", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0118", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2015? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B06", "B28", "B43"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0119", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0120", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 7 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0121", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2005? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A46", "B30"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0122", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0123", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2016 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0124", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2009? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A41", "A44", "B02"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0125", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 562.1001681479702}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0126", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.008089260808926082}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0127", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2014? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B03", "B07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0128", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number.", "answer": 2.002702702702703}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0129", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1199442119944212}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0130", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2017? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0131", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 0.4366892015348072}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0132", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0133", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2011 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Organic-Inorganic Hybrid Multilayer Gate Dielectrics for Thin-Film Transistors"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0134", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2013? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B04", "B06", "B30"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0135", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2014 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0136", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2012? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A23", "A41", "B03"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0137", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number.", "answer": 0.09700253430044568}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0138", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 9 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0139", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0140", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0141", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number.", "answer": 0.4782836668705759}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0142", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 224.18518914297928}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0143", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0144", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0145", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.5101813110181311}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0146", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR PRODUCING TLR5 AGONIST PROTEIN"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0147", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0148", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2012? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A46", "B03", "B07", "B22"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0149", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number.", "answer": 0.10039797395079594}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0150", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 9 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0151", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number.", "answer": 0.6541244573082489}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0152", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0153", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0154", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2013 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0155", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0156", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 0.20518911017723368}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0157", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 9 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0158", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 2.464827334186004}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0159", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2017? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17", "G11"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0160", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Matthew Marquez"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0161", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 2.533392698130009}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0162", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 0.1534845132743363}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0163", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2014 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 320.54893238434164}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0164", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 206.8345781588368}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0165", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 4 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2018? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28", "F42", "E04"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0166", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2016? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07", "B41", "A22"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0167", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 707.8019568151147}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0168", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0169", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number.", "answer": 0.23338802296964725}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0170", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0171", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2016 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0172", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2004? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A42", "B04"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0173", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0174", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0175", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0176", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0177", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 10 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama", "Tongliang Liu"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0178", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.05160390516039052}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0179", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2011? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B06", "B07", "B61"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0180", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0181", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number.", "answer": 14.380566801619434}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0182", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 9 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0183", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have greater than or equal to 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.32719665271966525}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0184", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2012? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A46", "B03", "B07", "B22"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0185", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2016 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 499.6364164086687}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0186", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0187", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 2.289958158995816}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0188", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2009 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0189", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2007? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A46", "B04", "B07", "B09"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0190", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0191", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0192", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2012? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A46"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0193", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0194", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 3 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0195", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2014 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0196", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0197", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0198", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 2.4933214603739984}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0199", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0200", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2004? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A42", "B04"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0201", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number.", "answer": 0.22622622622622623}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0202", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 8 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0203", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number.", "answer": 0.06953828828828829}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0204", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR PRODUCING TLR5 AGONIST PROTEIN"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0205", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2017 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 289.35227272727275}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0206", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have more than 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.12831241283124128}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0207", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 5.841037822035447}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0208", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2017? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0209", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.7927475592747559}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0210", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2014? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B03", "B07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0211", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2009 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0212", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have greater than or equal to 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.891213389121339}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0213", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 575.5098376783079}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0214", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2016? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07", "B41", "A22"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0215", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0216", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2016 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 481.559306229019}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0217", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0218", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0219", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2004? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A42", "B04", "B07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0220", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0221", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0222", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0223", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2006 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Automatic audio track setup"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0224", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2013? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B04", "B06", "B30"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0225", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2012? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A23", "A41"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0226", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number.", "answer": 7.532104969290899}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0227", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number.", "answer": 0.07476226226226226}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0228", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.008089260808926082}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0229", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 28.466607301869992}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0230", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2014 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 317.93790760869564}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0231", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0232", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2012 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 110.72012877348533}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0233", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have more than 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.03430962343096234}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0234", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0235", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 1.080109417741305}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0236", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0237", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0238", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0239", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number.", "answer": 1.3344500279173646}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0240", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0241", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number.", "answer": 0.6197654941373534}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0242", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 0.20518911017723368}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0243", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2018? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28", "F42", "E04", "F21"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0244", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.05160390516039052}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0245", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2016? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0246", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0247", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2014 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0248", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2011 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 160.51191823575815}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0249", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama", "Tongliang Liu"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0250", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0251", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2012 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0252", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2011? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A63", "F24", "G01"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0253", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "Photo-Based Unlock Patterns"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0254", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Matthew Marquez"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0255", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9656903765690377}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0256", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2013? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B04", "B06"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0257", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2017 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 343.4315992292871}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0258", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number.", "answer": 2.793672987852836}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0259", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0260", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2006 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 70.99336739873439}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0261", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0262", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2014 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0263", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 0.39339048672566373}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0264", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 5.100418410041841}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0265", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0266", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 7 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0267", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2016? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0268", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 1.4153761061946903}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0269", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9656903765690377}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0270", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2014 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 224.18518914297928}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0271", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1199442119944212}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0272", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0273", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0274", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2011 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0275", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 320.54893238434164}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0276", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0277", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2015 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0278", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0279", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0280", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have exactly 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07894002789400278}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0281", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2017? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17", "G11", "B41"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0282", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0283", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number.", "answer": 0.7587842846553002}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0284", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 0.27354435326299337}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0285", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR PRODUCING TLR5 AGONIST PROTEIN"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0286", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2014 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0287", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0288", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0289", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2016 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 481.559306229019}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0290", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 9 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0291", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have more than 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0292", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2010 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 157.60914662894862}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0293", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0294", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 9 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0295", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2007? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A46", "B04"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0296", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0297", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.008089260808926082}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0298", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have greater than or equal to 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9919107391910739}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0299", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number.", "answer": 0.09212469237079574}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0300", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 2.464827334186004}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0301", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2018? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0302", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 7 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0303", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2010 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0304", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2010 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0305", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number.", "answer": 0.39472759226713533}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0306", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number.", "answer": 0.08899524524524524}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0307", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 575.5098376783079}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0308", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 4 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2008? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A62", "B02", "B42"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0309", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2012 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 192.51526120937885}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0310", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0311", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number.", "answer": 1.106644790812141}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0312", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 0.10971082454083626}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0313", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have more than 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0314", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2009? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A41", "A44", "B02", "B03", "B21"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0315", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2008 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0316", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0317", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 1.5948352626892253}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0318", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2017 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0319", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0320", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 2.464827334186004}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0321", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number.", "answer": 1.1788866555973083}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0322", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2017? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17", "G11", "B41"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0323", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2010 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Telenostics point of performance pre-operations condition capture system"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0324", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0325", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have more than 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07670850767085077}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0326", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number.", "answer": 0.18236259228876128}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0327", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2014 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0328", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.18828451882845187}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0329", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number.", "answer": 0.3813188188188188}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0330", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number.", "answer": 0.24862361268898017}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0331", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number.", "answer": 0.0832468495181616}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0332", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2005 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 67.0113712588239}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0333", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0334", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 2.533392698130009}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0335", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.5101813110181311}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0336", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 206.8345781588368}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0337", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2015 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0338", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have greater than or equal to 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.20725244072524407}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0339", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2015? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B06", "B28", "B43"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0340", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2017 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0341", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2012 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 192.51526120937885}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0342", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 9 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0343", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2012 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0344", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0345", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2015? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B06", "B28"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0346", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2013 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0347", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number.", "answer": 11.417142857142856}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0348", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0349", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have exactly 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0350", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2015? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B06", "B28", "B43", "C13"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0351", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number.", "answer": 0.6396428571428572}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0352", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07894002789400278}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0353", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have more than 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07670850767085077}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0354", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0355", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have greater than or equal to 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.0502092050209205}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0356", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2005 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0357", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0358", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have exactly 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0359", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0360", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 12.012466607301869}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0361", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2012 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0362", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2009 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "DYNAMIC TISSUE HOLDING DEVICE WITH LOW PROFILE SPRING"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0363", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0364", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2013 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0365", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have greater than or equal to 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.891213389121339}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0366", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0367", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.7927475592747559}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0368", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2017 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 289.35227272727275}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0369", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number.", "answer": 4.284710017574692}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0370", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0371", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have more than 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07670850767085077}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0372", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 6 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0373", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0374", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama", "Tongliang Liu"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0375", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0376", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number.", "answer": 0.3201951951951952}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0377", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have greater than or equal to 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9919107391910739}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0378", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number.", "answer": 0.8945206676570829}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0379", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 2 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0380", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2012 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 192.51526120937885}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0381", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2013 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Photo-Based Unlock Patterns"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0382", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 2.289958158995816}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0383", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number.", "answer": 10.981981981981981}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0384", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2016? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07", "B41", "A22"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0385", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 0.38716814159292035}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0386", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number.", "answer": 3.0558347292015635}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0387", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 4.282845188284519}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0388", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 1.3213959437237346}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0389", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2014? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B03", "B07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0390", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.5101813110181311}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0391", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2017 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0392", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0393", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0394", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0395", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2016? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07", "B41", "A22", "G04"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0396", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2009 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0397", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0398", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0399", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0400", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0401", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 8 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0402", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0403", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0404", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have greater than or equal to 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.891213389121339}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0405", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 2.4933214603739984}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0406", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0407", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 3 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.18828451882845187}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0408", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2009 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 152.75797238633027}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0409", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 1.1715481171548117}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0410", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2007? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A46", "B04", "B07", "B09", "B25"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0411", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2015 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0412", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2011 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 88.16663164530364}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0413", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2008 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 147.29168502549254}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0414", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number.", "answer": 0.448974569319114}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0415", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 0.24764933628318583}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0416", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2006 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "Automatic audio track setup"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0417", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2004 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 101.14309776124641}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0418", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2018? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28", "F42", "E04", "F21"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0419", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0420", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Matthew Marquez"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0421", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number.", "answer": 2.6224774405250204}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0422", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama", "Tongliang Liu"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0423", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2014? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B03"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0424", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2013 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0425", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number.", "answer": 0.8945206676570829}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0426", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2016 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0427", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have greater than or equal to 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.0502092050209205}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0428", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2018? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28", "F42"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0429", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 3 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0430", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "METHOD FOR PRODUCING TLR5 AGONIST PROTEIN"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0431", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 6 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0432", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2005? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A46", "B30"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0433", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 9 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0434", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2013 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 206.8345781588368}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0435", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2012 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0436", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 7 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0437", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 0.5116024118399415}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0438", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 0.1749706916764361}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0439", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0440", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0441", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0442", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 4.787866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0443", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0444", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have more than 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.0502092050209205}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0445", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2011 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0446", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR PRODUCING TLR5 AGONIST PROTEIN"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0447", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have exactly 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0448", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2013 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 206.8345781588368}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0449", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2009 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 83.00395647873393}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0450", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0451", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have greater than or equal to 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0452", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2010 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0453", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have more than 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07670850767085077}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0454", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2015 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0455", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0456", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2012? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A46", "B03", "B07", "B22"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0457", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0458", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2008? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A62", "B02", "B42", "B61"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0459", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have more than 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.891213389121339}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0460", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2016 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0461", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0462", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2015 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 707.8019568151147}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0463", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2011? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A63", "F24", "G01"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0464", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2017? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17", "G11"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0465", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0466", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2005 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 122.00705477325958}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0467", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2016 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0468", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0469", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 1.080109417741305}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0470", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number.", "answer": 4.353571428571429}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0471", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0472", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0473", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07894002789400278}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0474", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 0.33047566371681414}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0475", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 0.27354435326299337}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0476", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number.", "answer": 2.4933214603739984}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0477", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have more than 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.03430962343096234}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0478", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 4 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2005? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A46", "B30", "B44"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0479", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2006? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B02", "D01"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0480", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.05160390516039052}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0481", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number.", "answer": 1.2201519536903038}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0482", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 3.123094958968347}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0483", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have greater than or equal to 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.702928870292887}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0484", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number.", "answer": 0.9258321273516642}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0485", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9656903765690377}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0486", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 0.40617577197149646}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0487", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number.", "answer": 4.604588394062079}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0488", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0489", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 2.0200986661794262}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0490", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 4 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2017? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17", "G11"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0491", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2018? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28", "F42"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0492", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.7927475592747559}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0493", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 9 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0494", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0495", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number.", "answer": 2.461988304093567}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0496", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2018? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0497", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0498", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0499", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2012? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A46", "B03", "B07", "B22"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0500", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 2.0200986661794262}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0501", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number.", "answer": 0.6295254833040422}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0502", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0503", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2006 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 134.79783403899881}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0504", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have greater than or equal to 5 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0505", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0506", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0507", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0508", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number.", "answer": 0.593273174733388}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0509", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2006? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B02", "D01", "D02", "D03"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0510", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0511", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2012? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A46", "B03", "B07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0512", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number.", "answer": 0.7939285714285714}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0513", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 4 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2005? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A46", "B30", "B44"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0514", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Matthew Marquez"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0515", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 4 CPC categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2015? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B06", "B28", "B43"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0516", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 134.04880703462894}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0517", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR PRODUCING TLR5 AGONIST PROTEIN"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0518", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 0.27354435326299337}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0519", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2011 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 160.51191823575815}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0520", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2014? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B03", "B07"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0521", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2004? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A24", "A42"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0522", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have exactly 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07894002789400278}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0523", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number.", "answer": 4.086785714285714}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0524", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2018? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A21", "B28"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0525", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.5101813110181311}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0526", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0527", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0528", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2005 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 67.0113712588239}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0529", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2017 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0530", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2015 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0531", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 609.4677191993234}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0532", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number.", "answer": 0.9258321273516642}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0533", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0534", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number.", "answer": 0.08228317272053373}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0535", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have more than 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.0502092050209205}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0536", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2010 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0537", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number.", "answer": 0.21617221418234442}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0538", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2016 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0539", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2018? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 317.93790760869564}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0540", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number.", "answer": 0.39339048672566373}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0541", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than 7 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.7927475592747559}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0542", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2013? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B04", "B06", "B30"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0543", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2007 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "WIRELESS TRANSMISSION SYSTEM FOR VEHICULAR COMPONENT CONTROL AND MONITORING"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0544", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 1.1179171551387261}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0545", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0546", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have exactly 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0547", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0548", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2014 with the longest time elapsed between filing and publication?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0549", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number.", "answer": 0.4698744769874477}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0550", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2007? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A46", "B04", "B07", "B09", "B25"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0551", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0552", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0553", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.026499302649930265}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0554", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 9 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf", "Dacheng Tao", "Masashi Sugiyama"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0555", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2012 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 110.72012877348533}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0556", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0557", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2012 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 187.3456972007973}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0558", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number.", "answer": 0.39015817223198596}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0559", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 8 authors with the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0560", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.008089260808926082}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0561", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2016 to 2016? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 538.8956416464891}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0562", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0563", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause", "Bernhard SchÃ¶lkopf"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0564", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2006? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B02", "D01", "D02", "D03"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0565", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have exactly 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.026499302649930265}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0566", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0567", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have greater than or equal to 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.12831241283124128}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0568", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 10 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao", "Jinman Zhao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Matthew Marquez"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0569", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2017? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 575.5098376783079}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0570", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2012 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0571", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 5 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2009? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A41", "A44", "B02", "B03", "B21"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0572", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.008089260808926082}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0573", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0574", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have exactly 10 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.015899581589958158}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0575", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 5 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2017? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17", "G11", "B41"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0576", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have greater than or equal to 4 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.702928870292887}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0577", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2008 to 2015? Return a float representing the number of days.", "answer": 79.43075117370893}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0578", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 4 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2017? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["B81", "B28", "F17", "G11"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0579", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number.", "answer": 1.0117117117117118}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0580", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number.", "answer": 1.31789761625635}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0581", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number.", "answer": 2.5225225225225225}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0582", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number.", "answer": 5.841037822035447}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0583", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 6 authors had the most publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0584", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay?", "answer": "EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0585", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0586", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 3 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2015? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["A22", "B06", "B28"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0587", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 6 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar", "Hao Wang", "Andreas Krause"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0588", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0589", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 2 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0590", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Han", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0591", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 6 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0592", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have more than 6 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.20725244072524407}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0593", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of papers have fewer than or equal to 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0594", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 7 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Baolin Peng", "Christopher RÃ©", "Jianfeng Gao"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0595", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2015 that took the longest time to be published?", "answer": "METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0596", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of papers that have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0597", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest percentage of patent approvals in 2012? Calculate the approval percentage for each category, then return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["A22", "A23"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0598", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of papers have fewer than or equal to 8 authors? Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0599", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the highest number of publications containing 'Large Language Models' in the title at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Break ties alphabetically, return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-hupd-0600", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 IPCR categories with the highest percentage of patent acceptance in 2016? First, calculate the approval percentage for each category, then identify the categories with the highest approval rates and return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["D05", "D07", "B41"]}
